Asano-kun, Setosato, super fun!
Asano-kun is a member after all!
Thank you for your hard work
Thank you for watching!
Thank you for watching
Sorry. Sorry.
This might be the last one.
This length, this height...
Maybe for the last time.
I don't like it.
We're having fun, aren't we?
It's funny.
I miss the familiar songs.
Ever since I was president of the company.
It's familiar.
It's in our DNA.
Nothing.
It turned out great.
But the part where we do Gatsley
It's a nice change.
Like this, right?
Uh...
Find the leak.
Oh, no.
It feels sooooo good after about the third track.
It's so easy to apply.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Dream?
Oh, yeah, Dream.
Can we just stick to that for a second?
Bunkles, chiggers, free-runs.
Don't do it! Don't do it!
Bunkle.
Second one.
Second one's over.
And ta-ta-ta-ta-ta
Ta ta ta ta ta
He's going to put it on the front.
Yes, okay.
Thank you very much.
Yes, well, now that we're in the service of ever wanting to have a bead on it.
I would like to start with the attack, if you don't mind, Mr. Member.
Yes, please.
Oh, yes.
I'll do the super express.
You're going to do the super express?
I'll be a dreamer. I'll be a super express.
Don't look at me.
There'll be 3 of us in Dreamer.
Is it better if one of us is the main dancer and the other is the backup vocalist?
Back-up vocalist.
Asano-san, are you okay with the timing?
Yes, I am.
Asano-san, are you okay with the timing of your hobbies?
We're going together.
Oh, I see.
Okay.
St...
That's right.
Oh, I don't know if I'm ready yet.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Ha-ha-ha-ha
A-ha-ha-ha
Oh, that.
Do you have a tummy ache?
I have a tummy ache.
Why not go mentioning?
Boo!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
It's a big shake.
It's reaching out for me
It's like it's going to pop and disappear
Stepping out of the red tree
I need your courage
Sing me a song
Love live in the joy that overflows with love
Grandpa Soy Sauce, Sing the Lyrics One More Time
After all, it's only a short Depth of Human
Depth
Kimi ga ko preço no
Longing aanu aanu aanu aanu aanu aanu aanu aanu aanu aanu aanu aanu aanu az uria
g
job
y
sail
c
cherry blossom
é
car
ah ah ah ah ah ah
Thank you very much.
I enjoyed all of it.
It was great.
STYLING
Boo boo!
What a big swing you've got going on again.
I'm pretty sure you've made a lot of patterns.
Yes, I do.
So, I want to match and match and match.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
But I can do it.
Maybe. Thank you very much.
I look forward to working with you in the future.
Thank you very much.
I look forward to working with you
I look forward to working with you.
Thank you very much
Thank you very much.
Well, excuse me.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry. Please make it longer.
I took a lot of time off.
Take a break.
We have a numerical opportunity.
What?
They're coming for the numerator.
Do you have a pause panel?
I'm sure it's fine.
Here.
This one.
And the pad.
And a cat watch.
And that should do it.
Here.
This one.
This one
And you could also use a violin.
squeak squeak squeak squeak squeak squeak squeak squeak squeak squeak
Good luck!
Have a good day.
Good work
Thank you for your hard work
Thank you for your hard work.